https://mykonos-accommodation.com/privacy-policy.htm

Mykonos accommodations
Real-time online bookingsComplete List of Hotels
all Deluxe Hotels ***** stars5 star hotels Mykonos Town 5 star hotels Beach Areas Suites with private pool4 star hotels in Town4 star hotels around Town4 star hotels at Beaches3 star hotels in Town3 star hotels around Town3 star hotels at Beaches2 star hotels in Town2 star hotels around Town2 star hotels at BeachesTourist class Hotels 1 starPeaceful HotelsPensionsAll Self-catering solutions
Studios TownStudios around TownStudios BeachesApartments TownApartments around TownApartments BeachesApartments 1 bedroomApartments 2 bedroomHouses and Villas
3 Bedrooms4 Bedrooms5 Bedrooms6 Bedrooms7 Bedrooms8 BedroomsPrivate Villas with poolLuxury VillasSearch Mykonos Locations Hotel & Lodging Maps Choice of LodgingComparative PricesSpecial Programs
Luxury Mykonos NEWHoneymoonersGay Friendly MykonosWedding on MykonosSelf-catering for FamiliesAutumn & Winter on Mykonos Season Rental & long TermAccommodation in Greece
Unique Santorini
Fira (Capital)FirostefaniImerovigliIa (Oia)Beach AreasOther areasNaxosParosPopular Cyclades
Amorgos Andros Folegandros Ios Syros Tinos Rest of Cyclades Crete
Chania Rethymno Heraklion Lassithi Elounda Rhodes Northeastern Aegean Islands(Lesbos, Samos, Ikaria, Chios)Northern Sporades & Euboea(Skiathos, Skopelos, Evia)Saronic Islands(Hydra and Spetses)Dodecanese(Patmos,Astypalea,Kos)Athens
Central Athens Non-central AthensSouth coast of AthensAthens Airport & East coastTop Hotels in rest of Greece(Thessaloniki,Corfu,Nafplia,Patra)Tours to Archaeological sites(Delphi, Olympia, Mycenae)Aegean Islands BookingsGay Friendly GreeceGay Lesbos Gay Tours Travel Services & Info
Reservations for
Summer FlightsAutumn FlightsWinter Flights Spring Flights International FlightsDirect & Charter FlightsAir-TaxisDaytrips around MykonosGuided Tour of DelosHorse-ridingCar rentalMotorbike rentalBoats during SpringBoats during SummerBoats during AutumnBoats during WinterCook & Chef in Villas Yacht and cruises NEWThalasso Spa Center NEWLuxury Mykonos NEWGay cruise to Delos & RheniaGay sailing in the AegeanXLSIOR gay festival 2013XLSIOR gay festival 2014NEWInformation pages
Mykonos island  NEW
Agios IoannisAgios StefanosAgrariAno Mera villageElia Houlakia Kanalia & Cavo DelosKalafati Kalo LivadiMykonos TownOrnosPanormos & Ag. SostisPlatys GialosParangaParadisePsarouSuper ParadiseTourlos Search Mykonos Locations NEWHow to get to Mykonos NEWJMK-Mykonos AirportMykonos BeachesSports on MykonosLocal transportation on Mykonos:(buses, taxis, caiques)Mykonos road mapMykonos Town mapTourist InfoGeneral Mykonos info for gays & lesbiansRestaurants & eating out Mykonos night-life Mykonos Shopping P. Couteau's postcards & photobookGryparion cultural centreMykonos Harbours NEWMykonos Musea NEWCNN daily Mykonos weatherLanguages
DeutschEnglishFrancaisEspanolItalianoNederlandsEllenikaRussianArabicChineseJapanesePortuguesTurkceAbout Us: M.A.C.
Reservation formOn-Line reservationsSales ConditionsCredit card fax formPrivacy Policy NEWF.A.Q. NEWRecommendations NEWCurrency converterHappy clientsfor Travel agenciesSearch our webNEWsSite map: our whole webMAC TeamJobsPrivacy Policy for Mykonos Accommodation Centertravel & reservation agency on the island of Mykonos / Greece
Mykonos Accommodation Center” values the privacy of our visitors/customers and takes every known precaution to safe guard the information we collect from unauthorized use: we do not transmit any information collected by us to any third party/organization or company.The following is a detailed explanation of the privacy policy for "Mykonos Accommodation Center".WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT? "Mykonos Accommodation Center" believes it is important for you to know what types of information we collect when you use our site or sign up for one of our related services. We gather information about you1. when you fill in our contact & information webpage or send an email from any of our pagesin our main website: www.mykonos-accommodation.com2. uses & register via our real-time booking system website “bookings.mykonos-accommodation.com”We do not use cookies. When you register for any of our services we ask you for your email address, name, country, phone & fax, dates of arrival & departure, type of hotel or accommodation or travel service you may need. Each time you sign into our real-time booking system at after registering for a particular service, you will no longer be an anonymous visitor.WHY DO WE COLLECT THIS INFORMATION?We use this information in order to serve the needs of our customers. We also use your information to process your requests & reservationsWhen you return to our real-time booking system atthe information you previously submitted can be recalled, so you can more conveniently use the features/services you customized for other Mykonos reservations in the future.HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION PROTECTED? The website servers are mostly in the U.S.A. and in Greece and employ the latest in firewall protection to prevent unauthorized access into our information storage areas . For our real-time booking system atthe latest in encryption technology, including 128 bit SSL encryption is used, to ensure that any sensitive information that is sent by you to us via the Internet is protected from unauthorized interception. We maintain a rigorous hiring process to screen out potential employees with criminal backgrounds.WHO HAS ACCESS TO MY INFORMATION?We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except under the following circumstancesOur reservations dept. has access to your information in order to better serve you. Only judicial requests by a duly authorized court will require us to divulge certain information regarding you should that situation arise. Finally, should our company ever be bought or sold, your account information would then become the property of the NEW owner/entity. CAN I OPT OUT OF HAVING CERTAIN INFORMATION COLLECTED? You also have the option of removing any information from our email data base and   distribution list. You always have the option to make sure the information we have collected from you is indeed correct. We recommend, that you contact us first to discuss which information you may remove without interrupting the quality of service we intend to provide for you. You may contact us, by phone, fax, email.NOTICE OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. However, if any changes do occur, we will publish the changes to our web site and post a notice on the home page that a NEW privacy policy has been implemented. We will also take reasonable steps to contact you personally to let you know of the NEW changes. Should the company be bought or sold to someone else, we will take reasonable steps to notify you personally. You will then be given the option to keep your account open or to terminate. MYKONOS ACCOMMODATION CENTER ADDRESS: Enoplon Dynameon 10 (upper floor) end of Matoyianni (the main street)- Mykonos Postal Address: P.O. Box 58 - 84600 Mykonos-Greece Tel: +30-22890-23160 or 23408, , or 28160 & Fax: 22890-24137 summer working hours: all day from 09h00 22h00 / 9 am- 10 pm winter working hours:  09h00 21h00 / 9 am- 9 pm e-mail address: info@mykonos-accommodation.comlast update February 23rd. 2012
